Hello.
こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Can I ask you to tell me your name?
お名前教えてもらっていいですか?
This is Miyao.
ミヤオです
Miyao-chan.
ミヤオちゃん
Well, how old are you now?
えっと、今、歳いくつ?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
20 years old?
20歳?
Um, are you already working?
え っと、もう働いてるの?
I'm a student now.
今、学生です
Oh, I went to school.
あ、学校行ってんだ
That's right.
そっかそっか
It looks kind of stylish.
なんかオシャレっぽいね
What series?
何系?
I'm a fashion expert.
ファッション系の専門家やってます
I guess so.
でしょうね
What, what are you going to do?
え、何するの?
Will you work in sales after graduating from school?
学校卒業した後は販売職?
I agree.
そうですね
I think I'd like to live somewhere like that.
そっち系住みたいなと思ってます
I often do press work or design work.
よくよくはプレスやったりとか、デザインやったりとか
Looks stylish.
オシャレっぽい
cute.
かわいい
Do you know what you came here for today?
今日ここに何しに来たかは分かってます?
Eh, not really.
え、あんまり
Don't you understand much?
あんまり分かってない?
yes.
はい
I think I mentioned it briefly in our exchange earlier.
さっきなんか、軽くやりとりの中では伝えてたと思うんだけど
Somewhat.
若干
Somewhat?
若干?
yes.
はい
That's what I asked you to come to today.
今日来てもらったあれなんですけど、
It's a leverage game.
イカセゲームです
It's a cool game.
イ カセゲームです
Is it a leverage game?
イカセゲームですか?
If I had to pick one, would I lean more toward S or M?
自分どっちかつったらS寄りとかM寄りとかあります?
I'll stop by the sun.
日に寄ります
Close to the sun?
日に寄る?
Close to the sun.
日に寄る
It depends on my mood.
気分に寄ります
approach the other person.
相手に寄る
There is also that.
それもありますね
Depends on your mood.
気分に寄る
There are two patterns, one of which is that Miyo-chan will get mine within 10 minutes.
パターン2つあって、 1個は、みよちゃんが10分以内に僕の
The one that challenges you to see if you can make the most of it.
こと を生かせられるかにチャレンジするやつ
You can do whatever you want.
何してもいいです
Especially.
別に
You can do it either with your mouth or with your hands.
なんか、口でしても手でしてもいいし
In any case, if you don't want to go, you can just ask me something.
なんだったら、行かねえんだったらもうなんか突っ込んでもいい
But.
けど
Do whatever you want for 10 minutes.
何 してもいいです、10分間
He lets me live for the time being.
僕のことをとりあえず生かせてくれる
The second challenge is that I will take the blame.
チャレンジもう2つ目は、僕が責めるんで、
Have them endure it for 10 minutes.
10分間それに耐えてもらって
I see.
なるほど
If she wins, Miyo-chan wins.
勝 ったら、みよちゃんの勝ち
Either way, if the challenge is successful,
どっちにしても、チャレンジ成功したら、
100,000 yen in cash.
現金で10万円
We will give it to you on the spot.
その場でお渡しします
It's not an hourly wage but a 10 minute wage of 100,000 yen.
時給じゃなくて10分給で10万円
That's why I'm asking you to come today.
っていう感じで、今日来てもらっているんですけど
Which one would you choose?
どっちにします?
Well, don't say it.
えー、まぁ言うな
What should I do?
どうしよう
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
How are you feeling today?
今日気分は?
I blame you.
責めます
blame?
責める?
yes.
はい
Shall I blame you today?
今日は責める?
feeling?
気分?
I blame you.
責めます
Honestly?
ぶっちゃけどう?
How many people have experience?
経験人数何人くらいいるんですか?
Yeah, but tell me
えー、でも言って
...
Film hand?
片 手?
I say it's one handed, but I use both hands.
片手って言いながら両手動いてるけど
It's enough to fit in.
収 まるくらいです
How much does it fit?
収まるくらい?
Eh, I see.
えー、そうか
copper?
どう?
I feel like I've lived a pretty normal life up until now.
結構今まで普通に生きた気分になって、
I was at the stage where I was giving him a blow job before I started thrusting into her.
なんか突っ込む前のフェラしたりとかしてる段階でさ、
Do you feel like you've already made some use of it?
もうなんか先に何か生かせちゃったみたいなのあったりする?
there is.
あります
be.
ある
What kind of viewing syndrome was that?
それはどういう視聴症だった?
By mouth.
口で
what?
何?
Have you ever thought about doing something first?
もう何か先に生かせようと思ったの?
Or did the other person just say it?
それとも相手が勝手に言っちゃったの?
I said it without permission.
勝手に言っちゃった
Did I just say it?
勝手に言っちゃった?
I see.
そうか
How long was that?
それ時間的にどんくらいだった?
It was more than 10 minutes.
もう10分以外だった
About 5 minutes.
5分とか
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
This might be a strong enemy.
強敵かこれひょっとして
I see.
そうか
5 minutes.
5分か
Let's do our best.
頑張れっかな
What, are you good at blowjobs?
え、フェラ得意?
Are you good at it?
得意かな?
I'm good at it.
得意です
good at?
得意?
But, you know, my face is cute, so if I get hit while looking at my face, I'll just go there.
でもな、顔可愛いから普通に顔見ながら殴られてたらそこで行
I feel like it's going to be difficult.
っちゃ いそうな気がする
By the way, there is a punishment game for this,
ちなみにこれさ、罰ゲーム一応があって、
If I could make it work in 10 minutes, I would have paid 100,000 yen.
10分で生かせられると全然10万円お支払いしてるんですけど、
Of course, since I work part-time at a public school, there are punishment games,
もちろん公学バイトなんで罰ゲームもあって、
When I fail, I just turn the video around and just do it like that.
失敗した時、ちょっとビデオ回してまんまでそのままハメ撮りさ
There's a punishment game where you have to let someone know.
せて もらうという罰ゲームがあるんですけど
There's a punishment game.
罰ゲームがあるんですね
How about that?
そこどう?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
If I lose, I'll just stick Shabchis' dick in the opposite direction.
負けたら、普通に逆に今までシャブチスのチンポをそのまま突っ込
Please be comfortable.
ま れる形になってください
Does it look okay?
大丈夫そうですか?
I mostly put the finish inside.
フィニッシュはおぼっきり中に出しますけど
yes.
はい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
So, Mei-chan, as a challenge, how about you make the most of me in 10 minutes?
じゃあ、めいちゃん、チャレンジ的には10分間で僕のことを生か
The challenge was to ask someone to do something for me.
して もらうっていうチャレンジで
I will do my best.
頑張ります
There are also punishment games.
罰ゲームもありで
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Well then, let's do our best.
じゃあ、頑張ろうか
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Are you ready?
準備整いました?
yes.
はい
Will you come?
やってきますか?
So, in taking on the challenge,
じゃあ、チャレンジするにあたって、
Can I ask you to tell me your enthusiasm?
意気込みを教えてもらっていいですか?
Well, let me go, I'll use the extra 100,000 yen.
えー、行かせて、10万円余裕でも使います
Did I say you can afford it?
余裕でって言った?
I can afford it.
余裕で
Well then, shall we go?
じゃあ、行きますか
10 minutes.
10分ね
yes.
はい
Take your time and start.
余裕、スタート
Your skin is so beautiful.
肌めっちゃ綺麗だね
It's true.
本当です
How many cups?
何カップ?
It's a C cup.
Cカップです
Eh, slender sound.
えー、スレンダーの音
I talk to her a lot, but I start counting the time by another 10 minutes.
俺結構話しかけていくけどさ、時間をもう10分カウントしていく
from.
から
Can I take this off?
これ 脱がせていいの?
Fine, not at all.
いいよ、全然
If you can get them to go in 10 minutes, you win.
10分間で行かせられれば勝ちなんだよ
Whatever you do, dude.
何したっていいっすよ、やつ
It doesn't matter what you do,
何したっていいっすよ、
Guy.
や つ
I'm salivating a lot.
唾液めっちゃ出るんだよ
Wow, that warm mouth.
すげえ、あったかい口
It depends on the ultra leverage.
ウルトライカセにかかってんじゃん
I'm really serious.
めっちゃ本気なんだよ
After 7 more minutes, I can take this girl's clothes off and put this dick in her normally.
あと7分経ったら、この子脱がして普通にこのチンチン入れられる
When I think about it, I get really excited.
と思 うと、すげえ興奮するんだよ
Let's do our best.
頑張ろうって
I might get excited if you hear it with my eyes.
こっち目で鳴らされたら、俺興奮するかもな
How serious are you now?
今 本気度何パーぐらい?
Well, 80 percent.
えー、80パー
It's been exactly 5 minutes now, are you okay?
今さ、ちょうど5分経ったけど大丈夫?
There's only 5 minutes left.
あと5分しかないけど
There isn't.
ないじゃん
Ah, serious mode.
あ、本気モード
I'm 100% serious.
本気の100%だ
It'll be 100.
100になるよ
yeah?
ん?
Wait, you're still my boyfriend, so you already told me?
え、まだに彼氏だからもう言ってた?
Yeah, maybe.
うん、たぶん
That's strange.
おかしいね
Kei is waiting for you.
けいが待ってんじゃん
I'm so excited when I think that Miyo-chan will come out inside me in just over a minute.
あと1分ちょいで、みよちゃん生中で抜けるって思うとすげえ興奮
I did it.
する んだ
30 seconds left.
あと30秒
It's over.
終了です
It was no good.
ダメだった
No way, 80% all at once.
ダメだよ、80パーとか一気に
Is it finally full power?
最後はもうフルパワー?
Yes, it was at full power.
うん、フルパワーだったけど
It was no good.
ダメだった
That's strange.
おかしいね
Until now, it would have been 5 minutes.
今までだったら5分経したわけ
how was it?
どうだった?
This coming soon.
この近中
Is it different from before?
今までと違った?
It's tough.
てごわい
Is it tough?
てごわい?
It's tough.
てごわい
I really understood.
てごわかった
Here too, if you go for 10 minutes, you have to pay 100,000 yen every time.
こっちだってさ、10分に行っちゃったら毎回10万円払わなきゃ
Because I can't go.
い けないからね
surely.
確かに
I'm training myself to stop every time I feel like I'm about to go.
毎回行きそうになってたら止める訓練してる
By the way, just to confirm, did Miyo-chan lose?
ちなみに一応確認なんですけど、みよちゃん負けた?
Yeah.
うん
You lost, right?
負けたよね
What will you do if you lose?
負けたら何するんだっけ?
sex.
セックス
The continuation is over.
続き終了じゃん
Yeah.
うん
I'm pretty sure that if someone told me to chew, I probably would have taken a quick attack.
確信ながらチューとかされたら、俺たぶん速攻行ったんだよ
Chew is terrible.
チューやばくてさ
Yeah.
うん
Born?
生まれっか
It's been less than 10 minutes, I think.
交代してさ、10分経てないよ、たぶん
Even if it was the other way around, I still won.
逆でやっても俺の勝ちだったね
I wish I was the one to attack, until things get tough.
俺は攻める方だったらなぁ、やばい時まで
Maybe there was a toy, but I can't afford to use it at all.
たぶんおもちゃあったんだけど、それ使うんでも全然余裕だね
Eh, which one?
えー、どっちだろう
clean?
クリーン?
clean.
クリーン
Yeah.
うん
Shikaha?
シカハ?
It hasn't even been 3 minutes since I put this in.
これ入れてから3分経ってないですけど
Today, in the first place, at Souro.
今日 そもそもソウローで
If we had played this way, we would have lost in a quick attack.
こっちしてたら速攻で負けだったんだよ
There's no need to be in a hurry this time, so just take a quick look.
今回急ぎじゃなくていいから、ちょっとペラして
I did that earlier, attack the nipples a little bit.
さっきのあれやったよ、ちょっと乳首攻めて
Wouldn't it have been better to attack slowly if you didn't go so hard?
ガシガシやんないで、これゆっくりやられてる方が速攻でいったか
too.
も
Yeah.
うん
That's so fluent.
その ペラペラやばい
Yeah.
うん
a,
あ、
It feels super good.
超 気持ちいい
Get behind me and let me see what we got in there.
後ろ手についてさ、私たち入ったやつを見せてよ
I was a little disappointed in the prize money, but what was it like?
ちょっと賞金は残念でしたけど、どうでした?
game.
ゲーム
it was fun.
楽しかった
As a result, I was able to have fun and feel good even though it was okay.
結果オーライでも楽しく気持ちよくなれたっていう
Feeling.
感じ
How high is this cock level?
この チンポレベル的にレベルどんくらい?
level?
レベル?
10 steps?
10段階?
10 stages.
10段階
8?
Was there a stronger one?
もっと強いのいた?
secret.
秘密
Was there an amazing one?
すごいのいた?
Yes, I'm sure.
だな、きっと
I wonder if about 8 levels is just right?
8段階くらいがちょうどいいのかな?
Hey, I'll let you know if another big-ticket game comes up.
ちょっと 次、また高額ゲーム企画出たら一応ご連絡するんで、
Please perform again at that time.
その時また再出演お願いします
Thank you again for your hard work today.
今日またお疲れさまでした
thank you.
ありがとうございます